<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Garone Businesly Tips</string>
    <string name="busi1_article">Don\'t rely on your financial literacy</string>
    <string name="busi1_desx">Many entrepreneurs try to save on everything. And even accounting services. Such savings are fraught not only with a million spent damaged nerve cells, but also with serious skin diseases. Ignorance of the relevance of the submitted documents of the Ukrainian tax code, the average size of the camera, inability to keep a financial report, etc. includes many fines from the tax office, shortcomings and more. Therefore, saving on the services of an experienced accountant is not worth it. If a young company cannot afford a regular inspection, you can use the services of an accounting audit.</string>
    <string name="busi2_article">Always be on the road</string>
    <string name="busi2_desc">At the initial stage, it is important to make quick decisions. Meet with a potential supplier, register an application with the tax office, give invoices to a client - and all this (hundreds of other tasks) must be completed within one day. Business problems require prompt solutions. And the car plays an important role here. The name "at hand" of personal transport, give yourself:
        Reducing taxi costs;
        Quick resolution of emerging issues;
        Possibility in a short time to get to any point of the city;
        Increasing the status of partners, customers.
        You can use these opportunities even if there is no personal transport. In this case, car rental in Kyiv for the period you need will come to the rescue. A rented car will allow you to quickly move around the city with minimal budget losses. At the same time, while driving, you will be able to think over the upcoming conversation in a calm atmosphere, develop a unique promotion strategy, and more. No annoying conversations and no annoying radio.
    </string>
    <string name="busi3_article">Grow your brand online</string>
    <string name="busi3_desc">mmediately after the start of sales / production / services, create your site and actively promote it. This will surely help you reach a wide audience and quickly reach your desired income level. Every third potential customer searches for a service/product on the Internet and only then comes to the store/company itself to make a purchase.
        If the initial budget is limited, replace the site with an account on social networks. You can decorate it beautifully on your own. Automatic systems can help you without using targeted advertising assistance to a specific target audience (selected by age, geolocation, interests, gender, and more).</string>
    <string name="busi4_article">Work in the office</string>
    <string name="busi4_desc">You can manage business processes and employees remotely only if the company’s activities are already automated, and deputies do most of the work for you. In other cases, it is recommended to work in a full-fledged office. This will allow you:
        Supervise the work performed by employees;
        Always have a print, printer, fax, PC at hand;
        Hold meetings with partners / clients in a convenient place.
       Additionally, renting an office will increase the status of the company and cause a positive attitude towards it from others. Clients and partners are more loyal to firms that occupy decent office space. it is believed that she is inclined to work more responsibly and more seriously. This stereotype was formed in pre-Internet times. It is still relevant and not followed is a real crime.
    </string>
    <string name="busi5_article">Be disciplined</string>
    <string name="busi5_desc">One of the most widespread cases of infection in the world said: “We do not need to be smarter than the rest. We must be more disciplined than the rest." Always keep this phrase in mind and remember that results achieve results that stubbornly go to their goal and clearly build a work schedule. To make this possible, you need:
        Have a busy place;
        Assemble a team of experienced employees;
        Always be in touch and be able to come anywhere in the city.
        The success of a businessman depends on his discipline, attitude to his business. Do not be afraid to invest everything in the company: time, money, effort. In the early stages, this is quite normal. And the more you invest in the venture in the beginning, the more profit you will receive at a lower cost in the future.
        Building your own business is an art. Most entrepreneurs give up in the first year of their business development. Not to become one of them will help efficiency in resolving issues, the help of professionals, strict discipline and a comfortable workplace.
    </string>
</resources>